Data set:
	WARC
Description: 
	Tools for the WARC file format for storing web archives
Source: 
	high level reqs. (FRS+NFR)
Target: 
	low level reqs. (SRS)

Directory structure
	answer.csv: answer matrix file (136 links)
	high: directory that contains source artifacts (63 files)
	low: directory that contains target artifacts (89 files)
	FRS: directory that contains Functional Requirements Specification artifacts (42 files)
	NFR: directory that contains Non-Functional Requirements Specification artifacts (21 files)
	SRS: directory that contains Software Requirements Specification artifacts (89 files)
	FRStoSRS.txt: Functional Requirements Specification to Software Requirements Specification gold standard
    NFRtoSRS.txt: Non-Functional Requirements Specification to Software Requirements Specification gold standard
	warc_tools_frs.pdf: original Functional Requirements Specification document
    warc_tools_nfr.pdf: original Non-Functional Requirements Specification document
    warc_tools_srs.pdf: original Software Requirements Specification document
	

Data source: 
    Kong, W.-K., Hayes, J. H., Dekhtyar, A. und Dekhtyar, O. „Process Improvement for Traceability: A Study of Human Fallibility“. In: 2012 20th IEEE International Requirements Engineering Conference (RE). 2012 20th IEEE International Requirements Engineering Conference (RE). Sep. 2012, p. 31–40.
