Data set:
	WV_CCHIT
Description: 
	Health information system
Source: 
	Requirements 
Target: 
	Regulatory code

Directory structure
    high: directory that contains source artifacts (116 files)
	low: directory that contains target artifacts (1064 files)
    answer.csv: answer matrix file (587 links)
	source.xml: original source artifacts file (116 artifacts)
	target.xml: original target artifacts file (1064 artifacts)
	answer.txt: original answer matrix file (587 links) 
	source2.xml: original source artifacts file (116 artifacts) in different format
	target2.xml: original target artifacts file (1064 artifacts) in different format
	answer2.xml: original answer matrix file (587 links) in different format
	

Data source: 
	Y. Shin and J. Cleland-Huang. A comparative evaluation of two user feedback techniques for requirements trace retrieval. In Proceedings of the 27th Symposium on Applied Computing, 2012.
