Data set:
	Modis
Description: 
	Open-Source NASA Moderate Resolution Imaging Spectroradiometer (MODIS) documents
Source: 
	high level reqs. 
Target: 
	low level reqs.

Directory structure
	answer.csv: answer matrix file (41 links)
    handtrace.txt: original gold-standard file
	high: directory that contains source artifacts (19 files)
	low: directory that contains target artifacts (49 files)
	

Data source: 
    Hayes, J. H., Dekhtyar, A. und Osborne, J. „Improving Requirements Tracing via Information Retrieval“. In: Proceedings. 11th IEEE International Requirements Engineering Conference, 2003. Proceedings. 11th IEEE International Requirements Engineering Conference, 2003. Sep. 2003, p. 138–147.
